翻译：饿得慌  zhanginfo  肉松  莎友友  幸田实果子
翻译：丁小七  横排混血  川川  葉子
校对：wdjmhs  慕秋雪    时间轴：紫熏   凭陵新月
后期：饿得慌    监制：wdjmhs
国土安全
第三季 第十集
美国空军及海军
Air and naval forces of the United States
对恐怖组织发起了一系列攻击
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
泛美航空103号班机于洛克比失事
Pan Am flight 103 crashed into the town of Lockerbie.
他已批准在非洲  欧洲和中东的恐怖行动
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe, the Middle East.
我们不容科威特遭受侵略
This will not stand, this aggression against Kuwait.
对于恐怖袭击的不懈打击
This relentless pursuit of terror.
我们将一视同仁
We will make no distinction...
美国军舰科尔号
The USS Cole was attacked
在亚丁湾港口加油时遭到袭击
while refueling in the port of Aden.
这是恐怖主义行动
This was an act of terrorism.
这是可鄙懦弱的行动
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
下面为您演奏的
The next samba we're going to swing for you
是一首经典曲目
is one of the good old favorites.
直到他受到了阻击
...until something stops him.
整个事件就发生在我的眼前
It was right in front of my eyes,
而我丝毫没预料到
and I never saw it coming.
该飞机撞向了世贸中心
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
成千上万的民众东奔西逃
Thousands of people running.
我们必须  也将在国内外保持警惕
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
你是我见过最聪明
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person
又最愚蠢的人
I've ever known.
我不是不明真相的那个人
I'm not the one who got it wrong.
我是唯一的明白人
I'm the only one who got it right.
拿下
Take 'em.
通通拿下
Take 'em all.
《国土安全》前情提要
Previously on Homeland...
那个袭击者是唯一可以证明布洛迪清白的人
The bomber's the only way to prove that Brody's innocent.
你他妈要干啥  卡莉
What the fuck are you doing, Carrie?
卡莉  马上回去
Carrie, turn around now.
这是对你的最后警告
This is your last warning.
她左上臂受了枪伤
We got a gunshot wound to the upper left bicep.
大出血  可能是射穿动脉了
Significant bleeding. Might have clipped an artery.
索尔在他妈什么地方
Where the fuck is Saul?
我们没想到他会变成那样
He's not what we expected.
但他是我们唯一的筹码
But he's what we've got.
这家伙有毒瘾
The guy's a junkie... sir.
我给你一个机会  再次成为海军陆战队员
I'm offering you the chance to be a Marine again.
不要再来了  我...
No more. I...
我已经完了
I'm done.
我设了个局
I have a play.
牵涉到了布洛迪
It involves Brody.
-你告诉过我贾瓦迪是个局  -他是
- You told me Javadi was the play. - He is.
布洛迪是下一步
Brody's the next phase.
什么局  你有什么好主意
So, what is it? What's your big idea?
达尼什·阿克巴里
Darnish Akbari.
伊朗革命卫队的首领
Head of Iran's Revolutionary Guard.
对
Right.
贾瓦迪的上司
Javadi's boss.
他还是和平的最大障碍
And the single greatest impediment to peace.
我想除掉他
I want him gone.
布洛迪能接触到他
Brody can get to him.
照索尔说的做
Do what Saul's asking.
-你希望我这么做  -对  是我希望你这么做
- What you're asking? - All right, what I'm asking.
瞧我这副样子  卡莉
Look at me, Carrie
你现在让我出去买包烟都成问题
You couldn't send me out for a pack of cigarettes right now.
我们会帮你做好准备
We'll get you ready.
但要你愿意配合才行
You just have to be willing.
他们押送我至边境处
The guys get me to the border
然后我示意投降
where I surrender myself?
没错  选择马里万郡
Correct, and we chose Marivan,
是因为很多基地组织指挥官
because several Al Qaeda commanders
同样在那里寻求政治庇护
also asked for political asylum there.
你凭什么认为我能够接近
What make you think I'll ever get close enough
阿克巴里将军并完成刺杀
to General Akbari to take him out?
贾瓦迪将作为引荐人
Javadi's on the ground.
安排你和将军的会面
We'll facilitate a meeting between the two of you.
我会从德黑兰回来的
I will come back from Tehran.
我知道
I know you will.
不只是为了她
And not just for her.
布洛迪
Brody?
到那边再见
See you on the other side.
卡莉
Carrie.
我想跟你谈谈
We need to talk.
谈什么
What about?
你的肩膀怎么样了
How's your shoulder?
焕然新生
Brand fucking new.
我想跟你澄清一下汽车旅馆那次
I want to clear the air after that clusterfuck with Franklin
狗操猪的破事
at the motel.
我没兴趣
I'm not interested.
这些鬼话早听腻了
I'm so tired of all the bullshit
都他妈明哲保身  没法和你说
and people covering their asses, I can't even tell you.
是直接命令  卡莉
It was a direct order, Carrie.
我是怕别人开这一枪
I didn't want to risk letting someone else take the shot.
你手术时候
While you were in surgery,
我看了你的病例
I took a look at your medical records.
什么
You what?!
我担心给你那枪的伤势
I was worried about the damage I'd done.
卡莉  你怀孕十五周了
Carrie, you're 15 weeks pregnant.
-那又怎么  -我想
- So? - So, I think
你应该考虑退出这次行动
you should consider sitting this part of the operation out.
为什么
And why would I do that?
因为在这种情况下
Because it's impossible for you to be objective
你无法客观行事
under the circumstances.
你指的是  我怀了布洛迪的孩子
The circumstances being, I'm carrying Brody's child?
对
Yes.
第一  这孩子不是他的
Well, first of all, it's not his,
谢谢担心  第二
thank you very much. Second of all,
这不关你屁事  不关任何人的事
it's none of your damn business, or anyone else's,
所以别他妈多管闲事
so just stay the fuck out of my way.
伊拉克  距两伊边境6.4公里
半熟
Medium rare?
味道挺他妈不错吧
Pretty fucking tasty, huh?
不错
Hmm... hmm. Yeah.
秘诀就是在宰羊之前
The secret is to relax the goat
让它们放轻松
before you cut his throat.
所以莫达勒斯才死得那么惨
Which is why Modarres has lockjaw and sore knees.
莫达勒斯:反对卡扎尔王朝的政治家
被毒死在监狱中
他们怎么样
How are they doing?
很好  顺利通过库尔德人聚居区
Good. That move across Kurdistan was uneventful.
目前
Now...
他们在这里
that's them right there.
等待日落  到时候
They're waiting for nightfall, at which point,
他们直接把他送到边境那里
they'll drive him right up to the border here,
掩护他越过伊朗那边的
cover him across to the manned checkpoint
武装检查站 就在这里
on the Iranian side, right there.
总统现在最担心
The risk of an international incident
引起国际争端的风险
is a serious concern for the president.
我们决不辜负对他的承诺
We stand 100% behind what we told him.
此次行动值得冒险
The risk of this operation is worth the reward.
万一出了什么岔子
And in the unlikely event anything goes wrong,
也瞒得住
we have it covered.
我可不想知道你们搞的那套
I'm not even going to ask what that means.
今晚他要做的
All he has to do tonight
就是过境  并寻求避难
is walk across the border and ask for asylum.
就这样
That's it.
在陆战队学的吗
Is that a Marine thing?
袜子翻个面  干面朝里
Turn the socks inside out, get the fresh side.
哪有干面啊
Well, there is no fresh side.
一面湿了  另一面也完蛋
One side's sweaty, and the other's just dirty.
也许是我忘不掉吧
Well, maybe it's just all in my head.
有用吗
Does it work?
你看我
Well, look at me.
焕然一新了
I'm a new man.
信号收到
Comms check.
A小队  这里是总部
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero.
有图像了
We have visual.
发送信号强度  完毕
Send signal strength. Over.
A小队
Kilo-Alpha.
信号强度10
Signal strength ten.
B小队  这里是总部  完毕
Kilo-Bravo, this is Zero. Over.
B小队  强度同样10
Bravo. Also strength ten.
总部  这里是A队
Zero, this is Kilo-Alpha.
新月  能见度良好
New moon, visibility good.
又见天堂啊
Another day in paradise.
乘客怎么样
How's the passenger doing?
不错
Not bad.
对于一个"锅盖头"来讲
For a fucking jarhead.
好的  A队结束通话
That is all. Alpha out.
B队结束通话
Bravo out.
他入境点是哪里
What's he walking into at the border crossing point?
基恩  请把边境图片拿过来
Hey, Gene, can you bring up the border photos, please?
马上
Coming up.
两小时前的
Yeah, as of two hours ago,
有个八人的兵营  某中士指挥
one barrack hut for eight men, commanded by a sergeant.
路边防哨由俩携自动武器的士兵
Roadside guard hut manned in four-hour shifts
每四小时轮值
by two men with automatic weapons.
伊边巡队无线电通信有新情况吗
Any updates on the Iranian border patrol radio traffic?
每小时互相通话一次
Hourly comms checks.
还有一通要求补充给养
Plus, one request for more ration packs,
两通要无线电电池
two for new radio batteries.
八个无聊饥渴的大兵
Eight bored and hungry conscripts
通话记录被我们尽收眼底
whose radios we're dialed into.
这样就不会低估他们的实力了
No chance of underestimating them then?
说得好
Fair point.
最后再说一遍你的台词
Let's go over your cover story one last time.
中情局爆炸后
After the bombing,
纳齐尔的人在那附近留了辆车
Nazir's network left a car near Langley,
我把车开进加拿大边境的森林里
which I took into the woods on the Canadian border,
我剃了头  继续步行
where I shaved my head, and I continued on foot.
在那偷了艘船穿过芬迪湾
There I stole a boat across the Bay of Fundy
到达新斯科舍  遇到了一个
to Nova Scotia, where I met a guy
和阿莫·艾马蒂有联系的人
who had ties with Amer El-Maati,
他把我装进集装箱送往哥伦比亚
who put me in a shipping container to Colombia.
然后  真主党雇佣兵
Then, mercenaries working with Hezbollah
把我送到委内瑞拉
took me across to Venezuela,
终于把我送上一架国有石油公司的飞机
where they finally put me into a state oil company plane
飞往伊拉克
to a strip in Iraq,
把我交到基地组织手里
where I was handed over to an Al Qaeda cell
他们的任务就是让我穿越伊朗边境
who were tasked with getting me across the border to Iran.
加入基地组织  游遍世界各地
Join Al Qaeda, see the world.
终检  夜视仪
Final checks. Night vision.
夜视仪画面传输中
Night vision transmissions coming online.
口香糖没了  你那还有吗
I'm out of Black Jack. Any more out there?
一切还好吗  长官
Everything okay, sir?
最后一包了吗
This the last pack?
给你买了很多
I got you plenty more.
别担心
Don't worry.
你写信了吗
Did you write a letter?
什么
What?
写给家人
Home.
说再见的信
To say good-bye.
我写了你们肯定会知道
Pretty sure you guys would know if I did.
你应该找那你中情局的朋友
You could've arranged it with your, uh,
那金发妞  帮你安排一下
CIA friend, the blonde.
你还好吗
How you doing?
很好  你呢
Good. You?
好像是在维加斯把房子都赌上了
Feel like I'm in Vegas betting the mortgage.
准备好了  大伙们
Stand by, people.
好戏上演
Show time.
死神一号怎么回事
What's going on with Reaper 1?
传感器带宽故障
Sensor bandwidth issues.
很常见  我们正在重置
It happens. We're resetting.
一切顺利  用不了几分钟
All being well, shouldn't be more than a couple minutes.
"一切顺利"吗
"All being well"?
要等无人机重连他们才能行动吗
Are we holding the team back until the drone's back on line?
无人机是给我们用的
That drone's mainly for us.
他们有卫星电话和夜视仪
They have satphones and night vision.
他们没有无人机也能向边境移动
They can move closer to the border without it for now.
-糟糕  -怎么
- Shit. - What?
去边境的路可以说被封锁了
Road to the border's as good as blocked.
外国人贿赂当地官员换取免费天然气
Foreign gas trucks paying off local officials with free gas.
警察  军队  你能想到的都受贿了
Cops, military, you name it, all on the take.
边境在哪
Where's the border?
从这条路穿过他们还有1.6公里
Another mile past 'em on this same road.
远方灯光处
Those lights in the distance.
A小队呼叫总部  完毕
Zero, Kilo-Alpha, over.
总部收到  完毕
Zero send, over.
看到了吗
See what I'm seeing?
是的  稍等
Yeah. Wait out.
伙计们  下车
Guys, get out.
让路过的人看起来是车坏了
Make it look like car trouble for anybody passing.
我们有备用计划  对吧
We have a backup plan, right?
我们等总部确认备用路线
Yeah. We're waiting for Langley to confirm the alternate route.
现在需要用无人机  能不能用
Now, I need that drone. Are we gonna have it or not?
收到
Copy that.
他们怎么这么慢
What's taking them so long?
不知道  他们的无人机出了点故障
I don't know. They had a technical with the drone.
那我们得在这坐多久
So how long are we gonna sit here for?
靠  老兄  你比我孩子还烦
Shit, man, you're worse than my kids.
天  那些躲在后方的傻逼
God, those Rear Echelon motherfuckers.
无人机出问题了
Got a problem with the drone.
开局真不错
That's a good start.
死神回来了
Reaper's back.
很好
Good.
现在看看那条入境的备用路线
Now let's get eyes on that alternate route into the border.
重新定位中
Repositioning now.
总部呼叫A小队
Kilo-Alpha, Zero.
无人机已重连  侦查路线中
Drone is back online. Scouting your route.
稍等
Wait out.
又嚼你的幸运口香糖了吗
Back to chewing your lucky gum again?
是啊  来一片吗
Yeah. You want a stick?
该死
Shit.
把头低下
Put your head down.
装睡就行了  别动
Like you're sleeping. Don't move.
总部  B小队已经就位
Zero, Kilo-Bravo. Stand by.
A小队的车子可能出状况了
May have a situation with the Alpha vehicle.
当地警察都出动了
Local cops just rolled up.
[库尔德语]
[阿拉伯语]
你在这做什么
Why are you here?
[阿拉伯语]
去马里万
Going to Marivan.
基地组织
...Al Qaeda.
[阿拉伯语]
他们不相信咱们编的故事
They're not buying the cover story.
[阿拉伯语]
天哪  他们要到卡车里面看看
Jesus, they want to look in the truck.
传口令  A小队
Say the word, Kilo-Alpha.
-什么口令  -"晚安"
- What word? - "Good night."
他们会在警察发现布洛迪之前说"晚安"
They should say "good night" before the cops see Brody.
愿安宁与你同在
As-salamu alaykum.
[阿拉伯语]
晚安
Good...night.
喂
Hey...
你怎么样
You okay?
布洛迪  你还好吗
Brody? You good?
喂
Hey.
-你他妈的干啥  -我不行
- What the fuck are you doing? - I can't do it.
-你行  -不  我不行
- Yes, you can. - I can't. No.
-他妈的  我真不行  -你非行不可
- I can't. No, I fucking can't. - And you will.
我真他妈的不行...
I fucking can't. I fucking...
现在装得像个雏儿似的已经晚了
Bit late in the day for your vagina to chime in.
滚犊子
Fuck off...
你害怕了
You scared?
你他妈的害怕了吗
Are you fucking scared?
我
I'm...
-我怕了  真怕了  -好啊
- I'm scared. I'm scared. - Good.
我也怕  我见过太多人
Me, too. I've seen way too many men
死在这种第三世界国家的厕所里了
killed out here in this Third World toilet.
他们每次送我回这里  我都吓得拉裤子
I personally shit myself every time they send me back here.
如果你现在不振作点的话
And if you don't snap out of this right now
我们今晚就得死在这
we could all fucking die here tonight.
你想这样吗
Is that what you want?
不
No.
告诉我你会没事的
Tell me you're gonna be okay.
告诉我这还算不上走投无路
Tell me that this is not the end of the road for you.
不  我要听你亲口说
No, no, no... I need to hear you say it.
我会...
I'll be...
我会没事的  我没事
I will be okay. I'm okay.
我很好
I'm okay.
我会好的
I'll be okay.
A小队  有状况吗
Kilo-Alpha, is there a problem?
"乘客"晕车了
Passenger got carsick.
他吐了一场  我们要准备出发了
He threw up and we're ready to roll.
晕车
Carsick?
这条是安全通讯线路
It's a secure sat link.
能不能告诉他们别说胡话
Can you tell them to just cut the bullshit?
他没事吗
Is he gonna be okay?
他他妈的会好的
Fuckin'- he's gonna be okay.
给你
Here.
把你脸上的血擦擦
Wipe the blood off your face.
A小队
Kilo-Alpha,
B小队  前进至候补交叉点
Kilo-Bravo, proceed to alternate crossing point.
知道了
Roger.
A小队出发
Alpha out.
刚才那三个伊拉克警察到底有没有被我们杀掉
Did we or did we not just kill three Iraqi police officers?
是库尔德游击队  别斤斤计较
Kurdish--not to split hairs.
杀没杀掉都不需要告诉总统
Either way, this isn't something the president needs to know.
我理解  相信我
Oh, I understand. Believe me.
立刻帮我接特战司令部指挥官
Get me JSOC Commander now.
自两伊战争以来  这片区域
This whole area is pretty much a no-man's land
几乎成了无人区
since the Iran-Iraq War.
有人来了
We got visitors.
-参议员  将军  -局长
- Senator. General. - Director.
-白宫...  -我知道
- The White House... - I know.
-他们告诉我你要来  -让我把话说完
- I was told you were coming. - Let me finish.
白宫派费思特将军和我来监察指导
The White House sent General Fister and me to advise and observe.
监察指导
Advise and observe.
联合特种作战司令部指挥官
The JSOC commander,
负责指导  我受总统任命...
to advise; myself, the President's nomin...
这次行动  希金斯是怎么跟你说的
What did Higgins tell you about the operation?
行动要雷厉风行  悄无声息
That this part was meant to be quick and silent
兵不血刃
and bloodless.
他全告诉你了  是吗
He told you everything, didn't he?
是的
Yes, he did.
-包括...  -布洛迪中士吗  没错
- Including...? - Sergeant Brody, yes.
索尔
Saul...
无论行动结果如何
whatever this turns out to be,
是英勇的神来之笔或者怎样
bold stroke of genius or otherwise,
都将注定由我来接手
I'm destined to inherit it.
所以既然行动已经开始了
So now that it's actually in motion,
不管怎样
for better or for worse,
我只能希望行动圆满成功
I have no choice but to wish it every success.
能借一步说话吗  参议员
A word in private, Senator?
失陪一下  比尔
Excuse us, Bill.
好的
Of course.
说好了给我留的空间呢
What about the breathing room you agreed to give me?
当时说得是  我推迟任职听证会
The deal was that I delay my confirmation hearing,
我照做了
which I've done.
我履行了义务
That obligation has been fulfilled.
你该感到幸运  索尔
Consider yourself lucky, Saul,
是希金斯给我们打的电话  而不是总统
that Higgins called us and not the president
或是他的国家安全顾问
or his National Security Advisor.
收到
Copy that.
Copy.
-麦吉森女士  -参议员
- Ms. Mathison. - Senator.
肩膀怎么样了
How's your shoulder?
医生告诉我你非常幸运
Doctor told me you were very lucky.
我很好  多谢关心
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
我只能说你一定是名出色的推销员
All I can say is you must be one hell of a salesperson
竟然能说动布洛迪这么做
to get Brody to do this.
在中情局  这叫招募
Here at the Agency, we call that recruiting.
给你看看
Here. Take a look.
离边境还有一千五百米
Border's a click and a half away.
经过那栋建筑还有三百码
300 yards past that building.
那是条浅溪  宽十二码
All it is a shallow stream, 12 yards across.
听着  我开车把你送到那里
Listen... I'm gonna drive you right up to it
我们都会看着你的
and we're all gonna be watching you.
你趟过那条河
You wade across that river
朝着那边的林木线走
and you head up to that treeline on the other side.
你一到那里  跟着林木线向北走三英里
Once you hit it, follow it north for three miles
回到伊朗的检查站
back to the Iranian checkpoint
也就是我们本来打算把你送到的地方
where we were originally gonna drop you.
你去哪里
Hey, where you going?
小便
Piss.
跟着他
Go with him.
我们收到了潜在的不明无线电
We got potential bogeys.
作战小队向南三千米
Two Iraqi Army Hummers
有两辆伊拉克军方悍马
three clicks south of our call sign.
A小队  向南三千米有两辆伊拉克的悍马
Kilo-Alpha, we have two Iraqi Hummers three clicks south,
不是重大威胁但需要注意
it's not a significant threat but be aware.
A小队收到
Alpha roger.
向南三千米发现一支伊拉克巡逻队
All right, we got an Iraqi patrol three clicks south.
没什么大碍但那边地势复杂
It's not that big a deal but it's difficult terrain out there
所以我们得迅速安静小范围移动
so we got to move quick, quiet and small now,
那意味着只有我和他走
which means it's just me and him from here.
其余的人留在这儿作掩护
Rest of you guys stay here, cover from this position.
有问题吗
Questions?
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
在你小时候
When you were a little kid,
你长大想干什么
what did you want to be when you grew up?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
胡扯
Bullshit.
每个人都记得
Everyone remembers.
你不必再管我了  老兄
You don't have to manage me anymore, man.
我知道来这儿干什么
I know what I'm here to do.
只是聊聊天嘛
Just making conversation's all.
那是什么
What's that?
没什么
Nothing.
那你想干什么
Well, what did you want to be?
我在德克萨斯州长大的
I grew up in Texas.
我只想骑公牛
All I wanted to do was ride bulls.
你为什么没骑公牛
Yeah, why didn't you?
我骑过了
I did.
骑过两年
Two years.
骑得我"蛋"疼
But my nuts couldn't take the beating.
所以现在我改行做这个
So now I do this.
真他娘的开心...
Happy fucking...
刚刚发生了什么事
What just happened?
总部呼叫A小队  完毕
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero, over.
Kilo-Alpha, Zero, over.
B小队呼叫总部
Zero, this is Kilo-Bravo.
A小队撞上了地雷或者简易炸弹
Alpha hit something. A mine or an IED.
你能看到敌人吗
Any hostiles on your screens?
稍等  正在查看
Stand by. Checking now.
目前没有
Nothing, so far.
长官  那个伊拉克巡逻队已转向北边
Sir, that Iraqi patrol
正朝爆炸处前进
just turned north, towards the explosion.
我们现在必须通知总统
Now we have to call the president.
等等  尘埃落定再说
Wait. Let the dust settle first.
不行  万一有发生国际事件的可能
No, any possibility of an international incident
我就必须通知总统
I must call the president.
你必须做的是保持头脑清醒
What you must do is keep a cool head
尽量不要惊慌失措
and take great care not to panic.
我们至少要通知伊拉克方面
Well, we at least have to call the Iraqis.
然后说什么
And say what?
让你的巡逻队绕开点
Turn your patrol around,
我们有队中情局特工  没知会过你们
we have a CIA team we didn't tell you about,
就过去执行任务了
operating in the area?
那架无人机装备了武器  对吧
That drone is armed, correct?
B小队呼叫总部
Zero, Kilo-Bravo.
我们离A小队近在咫尺
We're one click out from Kilo-Alpha.
收到  B小队
Roger, Kilo-Bravo,
请注意伊拉克巡逻队正在靠近你
be advised that Iraqi patrol is closing on your position.
长官  白宫来的电话
Sir, White House is on the line.
接到屏幕上
Put him on the screen.
迈克
Mike.
-我也许能解决这个问题  -请讲
- I may have a solution. - Please.
无人机上装备了四枚狱火导弹
That drone has four Hellfire missiles on it.
你是要我们跟伊拉克巡逻队交火
You saying we engage the Iraqi patrol?
我的意思是我们发现有基地组织成员
I'm saying we just found an Al Qaeda cell
在帮美国头号恐怖分子偷渡到伊朗
trying to smuggle America's most wanted terrorist into Iran
然后被我们的无人机干掉了
and we take them out with that drone.
上帝啊
Jesus.
如果他们死了这倒是个好主意
It's a smart play if they're dead.
他们要是没死呢
And if they're not dead?
他根本不在乎他们的死活
He doesn't care whether they're dead or alive,
他娘的只想把自己摘干净
all he fucking gives a shit about is covering his own ass.
-闭上你的嘴  卡莉  闭嘴  -操
- Bite your lip, Carrie. Bite it hard. - Fuck.
那个伊拉克巡逻队马上就到了吧
That Iraqi patrol is, what, a minute away?
我再说清楚一点  迈克
Let me be very clear, Mike.
我绝不会下令攻击自己人
I will not order a strike on our own men.
挂了吧
Hang it up.
A小队的车里有动静
We've got movement in the Alpha vehicle.
要不是车辆刚刚启动了
Either the vehicle just settled
那就是我发现了第二个移动的热成像信号
or I have a second heat signature moving.
第二个信号确实在移动
The second figure is moving.
他们活着  他们都活着
They're alive; they're both alive.
我的腿
My leg.
干他娘的
Motherfucker...
我的腿
My leg.
不
No.
-他娘的我的腿  -坐起来
- My fucking leg... - All right, sit up.
快坐起来
Sit up, sit up.
双臂交叉
Fold your arms.
跟我来
Okay, come with me.
电话  卫星电话
Phone, satphone.
A小队呼叫B小队  完毕
Kilo-Bravo, this is Alpha, over.
B小队说话
Bravo, send.
我们在国境线西边的建筑里
We're in the building to the west of the border,
敌方没有开火  伤员仍然清醒
no enemy fire; casualty is still conscious
但他失去了一条腿并大量失血  完毕
but he's lost a leg and a lot of blood, over.
B小队  收到  六十秒后抵达  完毕
Bravo, roger. Your location 60 seconds, over.
在高地架设一组机枪手
Get a gun team up on high ground.
我能处理休克和紧急止血
I can treat for shock and stem the blood flow for now.
小心顺着我们的路线过来  完毕
Take your time to follow our exact route in, over.
行动中  完毕
On it. Out.
想想你的孩子们
Focus on your kids.
傻逼  老子没有孩子
I don't have any kids, dumbass.
我只是
I was just...
随便说点什么  你他妈就像个小孩似的
making small talk 'cause you were being a fucking baby.
我们会把你带出去的
We're gonna get you out of here.
烟
S-Smoke.
给我来支烟啊
Here, give me some of my cigarettes.
我他妈就没料到会这么倒霉
I never thought I'd be this fucking guy.
我也没料到
No, me neither.
我他妈搞砸了
I guess I fucked up, T.
那就喝两杯
Beers on you, then.
我给他注射一剂吗啡
I gave him one morphine shot.
还剩一剂
He's got one left.
我们得快撤了
We got to haul ass now.
抓住
Grab that.
这儿  放这儿
Here. Here... here.
转身  回去
Roll... back.
行了
Okay.
-准备好了吗  老大  -嗯
- Ready to do this, boss? - Yeah.
好  所有人都撤回到卡车那里
All right, everybody back to the truck.
走  快走
Go! Let's go, quick.
伊拉克巡逻兵刚刚加入战局
Iraqi patrol just joined the party.
B小队呼叫总部
Zero, Kilo-Bravo, contact!
南边有自动武器射击
Automatic fire from the south.
有一个排甚至一个连的火力
Platoon or possible company strength.
叫他们尽量缓住局势
Do all you can not to escalate this.
克制还击火力  控制火力
Suppressive return fire. Suppressive fire only.
别把狗逼急了  引开就好
Don't put them in the ground. Just turn them around.
B小队呼叫总部  要是不赶紧救出阿齐兹
Zero, Kilo-Bravo, we don't get AZ out
-他就死定了  -伊拉克方面
- in the next few minutes, he's dead. - Iraqi call signs
向防线请求了火炮袭击支援
are requesting an artillery fire mission up the chain.
离我们的直升机多远
How far out are our helicopters?
八分钟
Eight minutes.
将军  您的意见
General, advice?
时间不够
Eight minutes is time we don't have.
就算我们联系伊拉克方面坦白事实...
Either we call the Iraqis and level with them...
时间也不够
Also time we don't have
反正左右都是个死
and every shade of blowback we can't afford.
所以应该边打边撤  坐上他们之前的车
So it's a fighting withdrawal to a secure LZ,
退后五公里  回到安全着陆点
back five clicks in the vehicle that they have left.
也就是说  任务失败
In other words, we have to abort.
情报行动结束
The intelligence operation is over.
现在这是一起军事行动  由你指挥  将军
It's a military one now. It's all yours, General.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
把人给我撤回来
Shoot the boys out of there.
收到  通讯检查
Copy that. Comms.
B小队  我是总部
Kilo Bravo, this is Zero-Alpha.
B小队收到
Bravo, send.
-我们会用狱火逼退他们  完毕  -收到
- We're going to push them back with Hellfire, over. - Roger.
给我撤退命令  狱火导弹将立即支援
Withdraw with Hellfire in support on your command.
我来下令  收到  等等
On my command, roger, wait.
他们要结束任务吗
Are they aborting the mission?
索尔
Saul.
是你运气不好
You had some bad luck.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
至少我们还有贾瓦迪
At least we have Javadi.
局还没破  还有希望
He's still in play. That's not nothing.
对
Yeah.
准备等待狱火支援  完毕
Stand by for Hellfire mission, over.
准备好了吗
You guys ready?
撤退  撤退
Fall back! Fall back!
我不会撤退
I'm not going back.
妈的  你说什么  你必须撤退
What the fuck? What are you talking about? Yeah, you are.
我要穿过国界线进入伊朗
I'm gonna walk across that border into Iran
你别想阻止...
and you're not gonna to stop...
给我听好了  我他妈的命令你撤退
Listen to me! I am fucking ordering you to fucking move out!
"乘客"拒绝撤退
Passenger refuses to withdraw,
时间不够了  请指示
and I'm out of time. Please advise.
别留下任何一个人
Do not leave anyone behind.
火力太猛了
We are under heavy fire!
伤员优先
The casualty is priority one,
"乘客"他妈的不服从命令
and the passenger is non-fucking-compliant!
将军  请指示
General, please advise!
让我跟他说
Let me talk to him.
能说服布洛迪不去送死的  只有她了
If anyone can talk Brody down off a ledge, she can.
好吧
All right.
把对讲机给"乘客"
Put the passenger on the line.
我再说一边  把对讲机给"乘客"
I say again, put the passenger on the line.
拿着
Take this.
Take it!
布洛迪
Brody?
布洛迪  你听得见吗
Brody, can you hear me?
布洛迪
Hey, Brody!
他们想放弃任务  卡莉
They're trying to abort the mission, Carrie!
我知道
I know.
转告他们操他妈的
Well, tell them to go fuck themselves.
不  听我说
No, listen to me.
这件事你自己一个人做不到
You can't do this by yourself.
我距离边界只有三百码了  卡莉
I'm 300 yards from the border, Carrie.
我能完成任务
I can make it.
现在越界进入伊朗  你会完全孤立无援
Cross into Iran now and you will be completely on your own.
实话说  我这边别无选择
Well, to be honest I don't see much of an option here.
选择撤退  重新部署
The option is to fall back, regroup,
之后我们会再组织行动
and we'll take another shot at this later.
拜托  卡莉  你知道那是不可能的
Come on, Carrie, you know that's not gonna happen.
你怎么知道
You don't know that!
现在  停止行动  好好考虑下
Now, stop and think this through.
你没有许可  战场上也没有支援
You have no sanction, no support on the ground,
甚至没有脱身计划
and no extraction plan.
你会死在那里的
You will die over there!
不  你错了  卡莉
No, you're wrong, Carrie.
你想知道为什么吗
And you want to know why?
因为你会来带我回去
'Cause you're gonna get me home.
不  不准那么说  不要把那强加给我
No, don't say that! Do not put that on me.
那简直是白日梦
It's a fantasy.
你会想出办法的
You'll find a way.
我对你有信心
I have faith.
就这样  挂了
That's all. Out.
别  布洛迪  布洛迪
No, Brody! Brody!
操
Fuck!
我们现在要他妈撤出去
We are fucking moving out now.
所有人  我们走
All of us. Let's go.
我不走
Not me.
他跑了  操他妈
He's gone! Fuck him!
现在发射狱火  现在发射狱火
Hellfire, now! Hellfire, now!
狱火即将发射
Hellfire firing now.
现在行动
Move now!
抓住他
Grab him!
拿着这个
Take it.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
把他带到着陆点  再来接应我  快去
Get him to the LZ, then come get me. Go!
操
Fuck!
他妈的狙击手
Fucking snipers.
他们总是最操蛋的混蛋
Always the stubborn fucking assholes.
我能给你赢得三十秒时间  穿过边境
I can buy you 30 seconds to cross that border
跑到那些树那边
and get to those trees.
我一开枪  你就跑
Once I start firing, you start running.
如果你停下  我他妈就开枪杀了你
And if you stop, I'll fucking shoot you myself.
有问题吗
Any questions?
-没有  -很好
- No. - Oh, good.
我数到三
Count of three.
一  二  三
One... two... three!
那什么情况
What is that?
他们被包围了
They're surrounded.
被谁包围了
Who by?
我们能从无线电中听到什么吗
Are we picking up anything on radios?
我是尼古拉斯·布洛迪
...Nicholas Brody.
我因为中情局爆炸事件
被美国通缉
我请求
在贵国得到政治庇护
那你呢
我帮他逃到伊朗
是基地组织成员吗
是的
[波斯语]
这些伊朗人说他们抓到两个囚犯
The Iranians are saying they have two prisoners.
能肯定是伊朗人而不是伊拉克人吗
Are we sure it's the Iranians and not the Iraqis?
百分百肯定
100%.
上帝
Jesus.
他们把伤员平安带出来了
They got the casualty out safely.
他情况稳定  已经坐上飞机飞往航母了
He's stable, on a bird out to the carrier group now.
还有点别的事
There's something else.
什么
What?
布洛迪成功越境了
Brody made it across.
怎么做到的
How?
他抓紧时间一路狂奔
He made a last second run for it--
一头冲进了伊朗的军事基地
headfirst into an Iranian military unit.
他没事吧
He's okay?
没事
Yes.
他成功了
He made it.
你呢  索尔
And you, Saul,
还依旧身在局中
are still in the game.
我会下地狱的
I'll be damned.
现在  这些家伙
Right now, these guys...
他们训练有素  将越境的任何人
uh, they're trained to treat anybody coming
都当成以色列特工
over the border as Israeli agents.
你被严刑拷打过
You were tortured...
告诉我接下来会怎样
...so tell me what to expect.
做好受罪的准备
Expect to break.
你当时撑了多久
How long did you hold out?
我不知道
I don't know.
我很快就失去了时间意识
I lost track of time pretty much right away,
不过大概有
but I figure...
七天吧
seven days?
这些时间长得让那些家伙
Enough time to allow the guys
改变了拷问频率和行动计划
to change their frequencies and battle plans.
我只是
I just...
希望能为你争取到这七天的时间
I just hope I can give you seven days
让你完成在德黑兰的任务
to get the job done in Tehran.
你好
Hi.
我能坐下吗
May I?
当然
Of course.
法拉  你是局里为数不多
Fara, you're one of the few people in this building
知道马吉德·贾瓦迪是中情局线人的人
who knows that Majid Javadi's an Agency asset.
我没告诉过任何人
I didn't breathe a word to anybody.
我知道你没有  我不是为这个来的
I know you didn't-- that's not why I'm here.
但你在招募贾瓦迪的过程中扮演了重要角色
But you had a crucial role in recruiting Javadi.
事实上索尔说  要不是你  根本不会成功
In fact, Saul says, without you, it never would've come off.
他过奖了
He's exaggerating.
但还是谢谢你
But thank you.
问题是
The thing is...
贾瓦迪只是我们计划的一部分
Javadi's only half the play.
而行动的另一部分
There's another phase of the operation
你之前并不知情
you weren't made aware of.
这关系到另一个线人  他的生死
It involves an asset, whose life depends
取决于我们能否在关键时刻从伊朗救出他
on us getting him out of Iran at the critical moment.
而我们原先的撤退方案
And the fact is our extraction plan
刚刚泡汤了
just went up in smoke.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
法拉  你在德黑兰有个叔叔
Fara, you have an uncle in Tehran.
是你父亲的兄弟
Your father's brother.
-卡莉  不行  -你先听我说
- Carrie, no. - Just hear me out.
不行  这太危险了
No, it's too dangerous.
-我们唯一的请求  -你们是在要求我
- All we're asking for... - You're asking me
将家人置于高度危险中
to put my family at extreme risk.
你很清楚这一点
You know you are.
你忘了我曾亲眼目睹
You forget I've seen firsthand
行动是怎样在瞬间偏离了正轨
how fast an operation can go sideways.
坦白说吧
Tell the truth.
你永远不会让你的家人冒这样的险
You would never ask your own family to do this.
我也许会
I might.
据我所知  你的叔叔也不是个
And from what I know about your uncle, he's not one
为了远离麻烦就袖手旁观的人
to cross the street to stay out of trouble's way.
他是温和反对派的成员
He's a member of a moderate opposition group.
不是扔炸弹的恐怖分子
Not a bomb thrower.
我们只求在德黑兰有个能见面的地方
All we need is a place to meet in the city.
确切说是安全屋
A de facto safe house.
法拉  我们的伙伴身在战场
Fara, we have a brother agent in the field,
即将面临致命危险
soon to be in mortal danger.
我们不该竭尽所能保他安全吗
Don't we owe him every chance to get out alive?
有人来了  有人来了
Someone's coming. Someone's coming.
我叫尼古拉斯·布洛迪
My name is Nicholas Brody...
我正式请求伊朗伊斯兰共和国
and I'm formally seeking asylum
为我提供庇护
in the Islamic Republic of Iran.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
[波斯语]
阿曼·贾思明
Ayman Jassim.
[波斯语]
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
准备好什么
Ready for what?
和我一起去德黑兰
To go with me to Tehran.
那他呢
What about him?
不  操你妈的
No! You fuck!
-安静  安静  -该死的混蛋
- Quiet. Quiet! - You fucking asshole!
-为什么要这么做  -控制你的情绪
- What did you do that for?! - Control yourself.
-操  操  -冷静点
- Fuck! Fuck! - Calm down!
冷静
Calm down.
[波斯语]
现在
Now.
我们出发去德黑兰
We go to Tehran.